export const lvl4 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `What district in Brisbane is known for its nightlife?`,
    answers: ['A) South Bank', 'B) Fortitude Valley', 'C) New Farm'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Fortitude Valley',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `What mode of transportation is most popular in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Buses', 'B) Metro', 'C) Taxis'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Buses',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `What museum in Brisbane is famous for its historical exhibitions?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Queensland Museum',
      'B) Melbourne Museum',
      'C) Australian Museum',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Queensland Museum',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `What type of water transport is popular in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Ships', 'B) Ferries', 'C) Boats'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Ferries',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `What market in Brisbane is famous for its local produce?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Queen Victoria Markets',
      'B) Brisbane Markets',
      'C) Southbank Markets',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Brisbane Markets',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `What park located on the Brisbane River features a waterfront?`,
    answers: [
      'A) South Bank Parklands',
      'B) Brisbane Botanic Gardens',
      'C) Roma Street Parkland',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) South Bank Parklands',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `What unique accommodation does Brisbane offer for tourists?`,
    answers: ['A) Hotels', 'B) Campgrounds', 'C) Houseboats on the river'],
    correctAnswer: 'C) Houseboats on the river',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `What famous festival is held in Brisbane during summer?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane Festival',
      'B) Riverfire',
      'C) Woodford Folk Festival',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Riverfire',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `What type of outdoor activity is popular among tourists in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Golf', 'B) Water sports', 'C) Mountaineering'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Water sports',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `What sports stadium is located in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Gabba', 'B) Melbourne Cricket Ground', 'C) Adelaide Oval'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Gabba',
  },
];
